Guide to the Archives Organization File Additional records, Section 2: Boxes 23-44
Archives Organization File Additional records, Section 2: Boxes 23-44
- Box 26, Folder (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: Constructive Labor Relations, Publication (Box 26, Folder 7)
    By Richard Lester; Edward Robie. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Can Labor and Management Work Together?, Publication (Box 26, Folder 7)
    By Osgood Nichols; T. R. Carskadon. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Joint Consultation in Service Industries, Publication (Box 26, Folder 7)
    By Humphrey Mitchell; Arthur MacNamara. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: The Botany Plan, Publication (Box 26, Folder 7)
    By Joint Committee on Labor-Management Relations. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: A Gude for Teamwork in Industry, Publication (Box 26, Folder 7)
    By Howard Coonley; Bernard Hallward; Ralph Loper; DuBois Morris. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Industrial Democracy at Work, Publication (Box 26, Folder 7)
    By Labour-Management Production Committee. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Joint Consultation - A Practical Approach, Publication (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Item 9: The Story of Five LMPC's, Publication (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Item 10: Descriptive Material, Publication (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Item 11: What Makes for Industrial Peace?, Publication (Box 26, Folder 7)
    By Ivan Willis; Clinton Golden. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Report of the Activities of the Louisville Labor-management Committee between May 1, 1949 and Dec 31, 1950, Publication (Box 26, Folder 7)
    By Committee report. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Union-Management Cooperation, Publication (Box 26, Folder 7)
- Box 26, Folder (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: The BLS Seasonal Factor Method (1966), Publication (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: How the Government Measures Unemployment, Publication (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: Revised Seasonally Adjusted Series for Unemployment and Other labor Force Components, Publication (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Item 4: Special Report on Unemployment Statistics: Meaning and Measurement, Publication (Box 26, Folder 8)
    By Raymond Bowman; Margaret Martin. Item is in English.
- Box 26, Folder (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Financing Unemployment Insurance in Michigan, Publication (Box 26, Folder 9)
    1960-1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Problem of Economic Insecurity in Michigan, Publication (Box 26, Folder 9)
    By William Haber; Paul Stanchfield. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Adequacy of unemployment Compensation Benefits in the Detroit Area During the 1938 Recession, Publication (Box 26, Folder 9)
    By Social Security Board. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Michigan Ten Years of Social Security, Publication (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Item 5: Charts and Figures on the Michigan Unemployment Compensation Benefit Program, Publication (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Item 6: Financing Methods Benefits Structure Costs pf Michigan Unemployment Insurance, Publication (Box 26, Folder 9)
- Box 26, Folder (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: American Voluntary Attempt at Unemployment Benefits, Publication (Box 26, Folder 10)
    By Bryce Stewart. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Unemployment Reserve legislation, Publication (Box 26, Folder 10)
    By Committee of the Department of Manufacture. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Why Labor Opposes Forced Worker Contributions in Job Insurance, Publication (Box 26, Folder 10)
    By William Green. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: The Financing of Unemployment relief, Publication (Box 26, Folder 10)
    By Winthrop W. Aldrich. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: The Needed Link Between Unemployment Insurance and relief, Publication (Box 26, Folder 10)
    By William Haber. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Company Plans for Unemployment reserves, Publication (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Item 7: Unemployment Benefit Plans, Publication (Box 26, Folder 10)
    By Committee on Industrial Relations. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Unemployment Insurance in the Economic Security Program, Publication (Box 26, Folder 10)
    By Frances Perkins; Harry Morgenthau, Jr.; Homer Cummings; Henry Wallace; Harry Hopkins; Edwin Witte. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Is Unemployment Insurable?, Publication (Box 26, Folder 10)
    By Frederick Ecker. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Unemployment Insurance, Seleced Bibliography, Publication (Box 26, Folder 10)
    By Helen Baker. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Special Unemployment "Insurance" and "Reserve" Study, Publication (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Item 12: Selected List of references on Unemployment Compensation and Related Subjects, Publication (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Item 13: Coordination of Unemployment Service and Unemployment Compensation Administration, Publication (Box 26, Folder 10)
    By Arthur Altmeyer. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Some Phases of European Unemployment Insurance Experience, Publication (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Item 15: Providig Reserves Against Unemployment, Publication (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Item 16: Unemployment Insurance, Publication (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Item 17: Unemployment Insurance, Publication (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Item 18: List of References on unemployment Compensation and its relation to Relief, Publication (Box 26, Folder 10)
    By research Library. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: A Comparison of State Unemployment Compensation Laws, Publication (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Item 20: Analysis of State Unemployment Compensation Laws, Publication (Box 26, Folder 10)
    By R. Gordon Wagenet. Item is in English.
- Box 27, Folder (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Labor-Management in the Federal Service, Publication (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: National Commission for Industrial Peace Report and Recommendations, Publication (Box 27, Folder 1)
    By National Commission for Industrial Peace. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Planning for Progress, Publication (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Labor-Management relations, Publication (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Labor-Management relations, Publication (Box 27, Folder 1)
    Outlook for 1970. Item is in English.
- Box 27, Folder (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: The Employer-Employee Relationship:, Publication (Box 27, Folder 2)
    By Robert E. Doherty. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Disputes Procedure in Britain, Publication (Box 27, Folder 2)
    By A. I. Marsh; W. E. J. NcCarthy. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Canadian Labour Relations in an Era of Technological Change, Publication (Box 27, Folder 2)
    By Jean-Real Cardin. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Faid Deal at Work, Publication (Box 27, Folder 2)
    The Conservative Approach to Modern Industrial Relations. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Labor/Management Relations in the 1970s, Publication (Box 27, Folder 2)
    By James Hodgoson; Matthew Kelly. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Guidelines to Victory, Publication (Box 27, Folder 2)
    A handbook on Successful Management Strategy and Tactics in Countering Union Organization Drives. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: The Independent Employee, Publication (Box 27, Folder 2)
    By Neal Drought. Item is in English.
- Box 27, Folder (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Issues in Labor-Management Relations, Publication (Box 27, Folder 3)
    By John Shott. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Riddle of Labor Relations, Publication (Box 27, Folder 3)
    By Frank Rising. Item is in English.
- Box 27, Folder (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: The Rationale of Labor-Management Relations, Publication (Box 27, Folder 4)
    By Herbert Blumer. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Labor-Management Relations in Hawaii, Publication (Box 27, Folder 4)
    By Arnold Wills. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Labor-Management relations in Hawaii Part 3, Publication (Box 27, Folder 4)
    By Edited by Harold Roberts. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Selected Papers from Arbitrationand Industrial Relations Conference, Publication (Box 27, Folder 4)
    By Murray Rohman; Joseph jenkins; Joseph Murphy; Elmer Walker; Richard Anton; W.A. Maggiola. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: In GM Forward Forward Forward, Publication (Box 27, Folder 4)
    By General Motors Newsletter. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: What organized labor Expects of management and What management Expects of Organized Labor, Publication (Box 27, Folder 4)
    By George meany; Charles Sligh. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Special Number - Employers and Labour Problems, Publication (Box 27, Folder 4)
    By The Political Quaterly. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: contemporary Theories of Union-Management Relations, Publication (Box 27, Folder 4)
    By David Greenwood. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Crisis Bargaining Management - Union Relations in Marginal Situations, Publication (Box 27, Folder 4)
    By Howard Myers. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Labor-Management Relations A Look Ahead, Publication (Box 27, Folder 4)
    By Charles Sligh, Jr. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Trade Unions and Industrial Relations in the Soviet Union, Publication (Box 27, Folder 4)
    By B. C. Roberts; Maria Feingold. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: The Three Cs of Steel Labor Relations, Publication (Box 27, Folder 4)
    By Conrad Cooper. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: A Common Interest and Joint Responsibility, Publication (Box 27, Folder 4)
    By Hines H. Baker. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Our Greatest Challenge, Publication (Box 27, Folder 4)
    By Walter P. Reuther. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Labor-Accent to Human Dignity, Publication (Box 27, Folder 4)
    By Don Francisco Ordones. Item is in English.
- Box 27, Folder (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Labor and the National Economy, Publication (Box 27, Folder 5)
    By Willard Wirtz. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Front Line Supervisor's Labor Relations Handbook, Publication (Box 27, Folder 5)
    By Stephen Byrd. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Labour Management relations in Western Europe, Publication (Box 27, Folder 5)
    By Bernhard Tacke. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: labor Management Relations in a Newly Competitive World, Publication (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: The Changing Climate of Labor relations, Publication (Box 27, Folder 5)
    By Charles Kothe. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Labor-Management Developments - Challenge to the Nation, Publication (Box 27, Folder 5)
    By Industrial relations Division. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: New Challenges for Labor-Management Relations, Publication (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Item 8: The National Labor Relations Act as Amended by the Taft-Hartley Act and Landrum-Griffin Act, Publication (Box 27, Folder 5)
    By Joseph S. Smolen. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Types and Variants in Local Union-Management Relationships, Publication (Box 27, Folder 5)
    By Milton Derber; W.E. Chalmers; Milton Edelman. Item is in English.
- Box 27, Folder (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Recent Extension of Collective Bargaining, Publication (Box 27, Folder 6)
    By B. M. Jewell. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Employee Representation on Management Committees, Publication (Box 27, Folder 6)
    By Roger Jewett; Robert Calkins; William Dean; C. D. Moore. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: War Production Drive, Publication (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Item 4: Paper Read by Robert Watson, Publication (Box 27, Folder 6)
    By Robert Warson. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Union-Management Cooperation in Full-fashioned Hosiery Industry, Publication (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Item 6: Studies and reports Series A No. 42, Publication (Box 27, Folder 6)
    By Joint Production Committees in Great Britain. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Union-Management Cooperation in War Production Programs, Publication (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Item 8: Union-Management Cooperation with Apecial reference to the War Production Drive, Publication (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Item 9: Union-Management Cooperation in Men's Clothing Industry -- Chicago, Publication (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Item 10: Making the Collective Agreement Work, Publication (Box 27, Folder 6)
    By Morris Greenberg; William Clarke; Clinton Golden. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Some References to Material on the Sevelopment of relations Between Railroad Management and railroad Employees that Emphasizes Cooperation, Publication (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Item 12: Union-Management Cooperation in the Railway Industry, Publication (Box 27, Folder 6)
    By Otto S. Beyer; Bert Jewell; Henry Thorton. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Industrial Leadership Under Current Conditions, Publication (Box 27, Folder 6)
    By Clayton Hill. Item is in English.
- Box 27, Folder (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Union Management Cooperation in Production, Publication (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: Should Labor Have a Direct Share in Management?, Publication (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: Basic Guide for Labor-management Comittees, Publication (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Item 4: A Bibliography of Union-Management Cooperation, Publication (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Item 5: Report of Mayor's Labor-Management-Citizens Committee, Publication (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Item 6: Should Labor be Given a Direct Share in the Management of Industry?, Publication (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Item 7: Whats Ahead in Human Relation's Industry?, Publication (Box 27, Folder 7)
    By Harvey Brown. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: City Plans for Promoting Industrial Peace, Publication (Box 27, Folder 7)
    By Roy Owsley. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Joint labor-management War Production Committees, Publication (Box 27, Folder 7)
- Box 27, Folder (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Employment Stabilization Plan for the Detroit Area, Publication (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Publication (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: Morandum to State Directors on the Replacement Schedule, Publication (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Item 4: Statement of Problem, Publication (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Item 5: Summary Statement on Manpower requirements and implications for Overall Planning and Policies, Publication (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Item 6: Employment Stabilization Plan for the Detroit Area, Publication (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Item 7: Directive No. 1, Publication (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Item 8: Commission Chart of Central organization, Publication (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Item 9: The manning Table Plan for Manpower Inventory, Publication (Box 27, Folder 8)
- Box 27, Folder (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Operating a Labor-Management Production Committee, Publication (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Item 2: Heads You Win!, Publication (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Item 3: War Production Drive in Lumber, Publication (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Item 4: Plant Efficiency, Publication (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Item 5: Check your Program, Publication (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Item 6: Good Food: A Wartime Necessity, Publication (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Item 7: Turnover How to Combat it!, Publication (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Item 8: War Production Drive, Publication (Box 27, Folder 9)
    Official Handbook. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Informational Materials, Publication (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Item 10: Honors for Production Ideas, Publication (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Item 11: Production Guide for Labor-Management Committees, Publication (Box 27, Folder 9)
    Ways of Handling Production Problems. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: L-M Suggestion Systems, Publication (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Item 13: Replacement and Recruiting, Publication (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Item 14: Health, Publication (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Item 15: Absenteeism, Publication (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Item 16: labor and Management Teamwork, Publication (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Item 17: You Know Tom!, Publication (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Item 18: repront Number One From Labor and management News, Publication (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Item 19: Progress report, Publication (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Item 20: Linking Worker and Solder, Publication (Box 27, Folder 9)
    By Waltz Disney Productions. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: Importance of Joint and Equal Representation in the Operation of Employee Suggestions Systems, Publication (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Item 22: Board Newsletter, Publication (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Item 23: Safety, Publication (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Item 24: Informational Materials for L-M Committees to Spur Greater War Production, Publication (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Item 25: Basics Steps for Forming an L-M Committee, Publication (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Item 26: Suggested Articles of Operation of a Labor-Management Production Committee, Publication (Box 27, Folder 9)
- Box 27, Folder (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Labor Unions and the South, Publication (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Item 2: The Supervisors Handbook on Maintaining non_union Status, Publication (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Item 3: What to do when the Union Knocks, Publication (Box 27, Folder 10)
- Box 27, Folder (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: How the NLRB can Stop Union Violence, Publication (Box 27, Folder 11)
    By Sylvester Petro. Item is in English.
- Box 27, Folder (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: The President's National Labor-management Conference, Publication (Box 27, Folder 12)
    November 5-30, 1945. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Mutual Survival, Publication (Box 27, Folder 12)
    By E. Wight Bakke. The Goal of Unions and Management. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Relationships and Adjustments Between Employer and Employes, Publication (Box 27, Folder 12)
    By Minutes of the Second bi-monthly Conference. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Employment management Employee representation and Industrial Democracy, Publication (Box 27, Folder 12)
    By Working Conditions Service. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Human relations and Efficient Production, Publication (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Item 6: Working Principles for Labor-management Relations, Publication (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Item 7: Working Principles for labor Management Relations, Publication (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Item 8: Working Principles for Labor Management Relations, Publication (Box 27, Folder 12)
    Second Series. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Fourth Series, Publication (Box 27, Folder 12)
    By Working Principles for Labor-Management Relations. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Human Relations and Efficient Production, Publication (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Item 11: Report of the Governor's Labor Management Committee, Publication (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Item 12: Industrial Leadership Under Current Conditions, Publication (Box 27, Folder 12)
    By Clayton Hill. An Address Before the eleventh Annual Conference on Industrial relations. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Current trends in the Labor Movement, Publication (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Item 14: Protection of the Public in Labor and management relations, Publication (Box 27, Folder 12)
    By E. Wight Bakke. Item is in English.
- Box 28, Folder (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Minimum Wage Laws, Publication (Box 28, Folder 1)
    By Donald Cullen. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Minimum Wage and the Woman Worker, Publication (Box 28, Folder 1)
    By Women's Bureau. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Data Pertinent to an Evaluation of the Need for and the Feasibility of Extending the Minimum Wage, Publication (Box 28, Folder 1)
    By Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Laundry and Cleaning Services, Publication (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Comparative Committee Print of Minimum Wage Bill Showing Changes in H. R. 3935 as Reported by Special Subcommittee on Labor of House Labor Committee, Publication (Box 28, Folder 1)
    By Special Report by the Bureau of National Affairs. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Educators Look at the Minimum Wage, Publication (Box 28, Folder 1)
    By Industrial Relations Division. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: How is the Minimum Wage Affecting Job Creation and Production?, Publication (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Item 8: Effect of Walsh-Healey Minimum Wages on Regional Industries, Publication (Box 28, Folder 1)
    By Ronald Charles Buehner. Item is in English.
- Box 28, Folder (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Why Wage Incentives Work, Publication (Box 28, Folder 2)
    By John Nickerson. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Incentive Wage Payments, Publication (Box 28, Folder 2)
    By Kendrick Lee. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Union Poolicy and Incentive Wage Methods, Publication (Box 28, Folder 2)
    By Z. C. Dickinson. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Experience With Incentive Plans, Publication (Box 28, Folder 2)
    By J. K. Louden. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Paving the Way for an Incentive plan, Publication (Box 28, Folder 2)
    By John Riegel. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Why and What of Lincon Electric's Incentive Plan, Publication (Box 28, Folder 2)
    By Whiting Williams. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Recent Experience with Incentives for Individuals and Groups, Publication (Box 28, Folder 2)
    By Robert Wolf. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Wage Payment Systems, Publication (Box 28, Folder 2)
    A Selected List of References. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Wage Incentives, Publication (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Item 10: A Collection of Articles on Wage Incentives, Publication (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Item 11: Some Factors in the Success of Incentive Plans, Publication (Box 28, Folder 2)
    By John W. Riegel. Item is in English.
- Box 28, Folder (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Incentive Wage Systems, Publication (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Wage Incentives, Publication (Box 28, Folder 3)
    By National Association of Manufacturers, Industrial Relations Division. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Supervisory Practices Associated with Worker Attitudes Towards Incentive Systems, Publication (Box 28, Folder 3)
    By Gerald Mahoney. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Wage Incentives, Publication (Box 28, Folder 3)
- Box 28, Folder (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: The Effects of Minimum Wages on the Distribution of Changes in Aggregate Employment, Publication (Box 28, Folder 4)
    By Marvin Kosters; Finis Welch. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Measuring Minimum Wage Effects in the United States, Publication (Box 28, Folder 4)
    By C. ST. J. O'Herlihy. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Minimum Wages, Publication (Box 28, Folder 4)
    By Industrial Relations Section. Selected References. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: The Minimum Wage Rate, Publication (Box 28, Folder 4)
    By Yale Brozen; Milton Friedman. Who Really Pays?. Item is in English.
- Box 28, Folder (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: A Study of Minumim Rate and Increment Differentials in Steelworker-Organized Plants, Publication (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: A Study of Minimum Rate and Increment Differentials in Steelworker-Organized Plants, Publication (Box 28, Folder 5)
- Box 28, Folder (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Incentives in Manufacturing, Publication (Box 28, Folder 6)
    By R. C. Scott. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Incentives in manufacturing, Publication (Box 28, Folder 6)
    By R. C. Scott. Individual and Plantwide. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Incentives in Manufacturing Individual and Plantwide, Publication (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Item 4: Incentives in the Paint and Varnish Industry, Publication (Box 28, Folder 6)
    By J. J. Jehring. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Paving the Way for an Incentive Plan, Publication (Box 28, Folder 6)
    By John, Riegel. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: A Survey of the Applicatio of Incentive Schemes in Irish Manufacturing Industry, Publication (Box 28, Folder 6)
    By David Walsh. Item is in English.
- Box 28, Folder (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Experience with incentive Wage Plans, Publication (Box 28, Folder 7)
    By T. L. Carroll. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Wage Incentives and Production Standards, Publication (Box 28, Folder 7)
    By L. Clayton Hill. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: An introduction to Job Evaluation, Publication (Box 28, Folder 7)